I was in Hollywood very much so, and when I started speaking about these things, my agents
dropped me from CAA and Gersh, and my publicists dropped me, and I started getting all these DMs
from folks like, you're doing the wrong thing, et cetera. As a comedian, Zionists got my tour
canceled. They would literally call venues and get the shows canceled. They impeded my tickets
from being able to be sold, so people were not able to literally buy tickets to my shows.
They started email campaigns. They had a truck with my face on the side in Detroit that said,
Amanda Seals is a Jew hater. I say all this because I am a US citizen, and these people are able to do
this to me without any level of ... What's the word I'm looking for? They're just impervious to
punishment. So the stage is already set where they are living in a different judicial system
than we are. I don't know if y'all see that yet, but they're already living in a different
judicial system. I mean, we have seen countless examples of Zionists harassing people, harming
people, saying all types of crazy shit, doing false flag operations on a regular basis and
not getting any repercussions, and yet we see First Amendment rights being completely obliterated
in the sake of people saying, don't spend my money on genocide.
Jen кас conocer more than just anything.
Jen.